Dottie!
Dottie 该死, 起来!
Dottie, God damn it, wake up!
闭嘴， T-Bone！
Shut up, T-Bone!
Dottie 该死的，Dottie 让我进去！ T-Bone 你给我闭嘴！
God damn it, Dottie, let me in!T-Bone, shut up!
Dottie!
赶快起来！
Wake Up!
Dottie!
开门！ Dottie！
Open the goddamn door! Dottie!
赶快起来给我开门！
Get out of that fucking bed right fucking now!
Dottie， 开门！
Dottie, open this door!
Dottie!
Dottie， 开门！ 。。。Dottie！
Dottie, please open the door! ...Dottie!
Dottie，我快尿在裤子里啦！
Dottie, I gotta take a piss!
醒醒，是我！
Wake up, it's me!
妈的！
Shit!
等等！
Hold on!
开门！ 来啦来啦！
- Open the goddamn door!- I'm coming, just a second.
闭嘴！
Shut up!
哦，卖糕的，看在巴依老爷的份上，穿上点衣服！
Oh, God, put some clothes on, for Christ's sake!
嘿，我又不知道谁在敲门！
Well, hell, I didn't know who you were.
妈的
Shit.
关上门！好伐！
Close the goddamn door!
你都不知道谁叫门，你就这一身去开门？
You answer the door like that,if you don't know who the hell it is?
你又不是没见过
Nothing you never seen before.
至少达拉斯一半的人木有见过
Nothing half of Dallas County hasn't seen before.
妈的，闭嘴
Shut up.
我爸在么？
Dad here?
他睡了
He's asleep.
Dottie 在么？
Dottie's here, ain't she?
Adele把你扔出来了？ -不，我想跟我爸聊聊
- Did Adele throw you out? - No, I need to talk to Dad.
她把你扔出来了？ 你丫又打她了吧？
Why'd she throw you out? Did you hit her again?
哪有， 我才没有打她
No, I didn't hit her.
嘿 听着
Hey' look,
你能去穿上点什么？
would you please put some clothes on?
俄滴神，你就别唧唧歪歪了
- My God, I never heard so much...
那太他妈分神了
- It's a bit distracting.
你的灌木丛（阴毛）正在盯着我
Your bush staring me in the face.
好吧，真受不了你
All right! Jesus.
去他的
God damn it!
自便吧
Help yourself.
这是啥？
What'd you do?
切了点三叶草？
Chop up some clover?
哪来的这玩意？
Where'd you get this shit?
从你那买的
I bought it from you.
是吗？
This is that?
你来干嘛？
What are you doing here?
Adele把它扔出来了
Adele threw him out.
又咋了？他自己会说
So what? The boy can talk.
我需要找个住处，好伐！
I need a place to stay' all right?
为什么她踢你出来？
Why'd she throw you out?
说来话长
It's a long story.
Sharra，给我一瓶啤酒
Sharla, get me a beer.
你丫做了什么？又打她了？
What'd you do? Hit her again?
没有，该死！我没动过她
No, God damn it! I didn't hit her.
听起来像你从来没打过她似的
It's not like you never hit her before.
关你屁事，Sharla
This ain't none of your goddamn business, Sharla.
嘿，这是我的地方
- Hey, I live here.
蛋定，好伐！
- Calm down.
听着，老爸，我必须接受你那光屁股老婆
Listen, Dad, I gotta listen to your naked wife
对我的审问？
- giving me the third degree?
你哪只眼看见我光着
- I'm not naked.
为什么你不让他赶快滚蛋
Why do you let her walk around here like that'?
什么？
- Like what?
都大半夜啦
- It's the middle Of the night.
她就挺着她那海獭皮出来开的门
She answered the door with her beaver puckered out
好像很随意的想跟你打招呼似的
- like it was trying to shake my hand.
你给我闭嘴
- You hush your mouth'
她又不认识你（估计这女的是个妓女）
- She didn't know who you were.
那不是重点，该死
- That ain't the point, God damn it.
我可不想Dottie见到她继母的私处
I don't want Dottie looking at her own stepmother's pussy.
够了， 我要去睡了
That's it. I'm going to bed.
我可不想听你扯蛋一整夜
I've heard all the shit I can take in one night.
晚安了您呐
Good night.
你个小屎蛋，我会杀了你的
You little shit, I'm going to fucking kill you!
住手
- Cut it out!
梦见俺哈！
- Sweet dreams!
老娘阉了你！
- ...kill you!
去屎
- Damn it.
抽你丫的大麻烟
Enough on the weed!
他就留一晚上
He can stay here tonight!
嘿， 老子想留多久就多久！
Hey, I'll stay as long as I goddamn feel like it!
他要敢留下，老娘负责任的保证绝对废了丫
If he stays here any longer, I'm liable to hurt the little bastard!
蛋定点洗洗睡吧
- Don't go to bed mad.
晚安！
- Good night! Fucker!
别睡死过去了哈
- Don't die in your sleep!
你才去屎吧！乡巴佬
- Goddamn hick!
这他妈是哪一出啊
What the fuck?
真他妈够乱的
- Now I'm in the fucking doghouse.
嘿，去穿你的裤子
- Hey, put some pamts on
我要跟你聊聊
I need to talk to you about something.
跟裤子有毛关系
- I need pants for that?
我们要出去谈
- So we can get out of here.
我可不想出去
- I'm not going out.
走吧，有些事得私下谈
- Come on, this is private stuff.
去他妈的悄悄话
Then fucking whisper!
去穿你的裤子！
I need you to put some pants on.
别想
- No.
赶快
- Come on.
我需要6000块，不然有人会来杀我的
I need $6,000 or some guys are gonna kill me.
你丫最好跑路，越快越好
You'd better get out of town, quick.
1000也成
- If you could just give me $1,000?
我可没有
- I don't have it.
嘿，1000块可能可以推脱一下他们
Hey, I could hold them off with $1,000.
这个，真没有
Chris, I do not have it.
假如不是老妈，我可不会趟这混水
I wouldn't be in this mess if it weren't for Mom.
这下好，她把我踢出来了
Then she goes and kicks me out.
你打她了，是么
You hit her, didn't you?
去他的，木有啊，木有！
God damn it, no!
我没打过她，我保证
I didn't hit her, I told you.
那她为啥踢你出家门？
Why'd she kick you out?
我只是把她扔向了冰箱而已
I threw her up against the fridge.
她偷了我二两白粉
She stole two ounces of coke from me.
瞎扯，Adele 不吸白面
That's bullshit. Adele doesn't snort cocaine.
她把它卖了
She sold it.
卖给了该死Rex，导致了后面这滩烂事
Gave it away to that goddamn Rex,'cause the shit's gone.
只有她一个人知道我把东西藏在哪
She was the only other one knew where it was. Then tonight,
今晚，她开着她那金灿灿的车来的，牌子像是Watch
she comes up to the house with her car running like a watch.
Which？金灿灿的凯迪拉克（Limousine Which)？扯蛋吧你
Which? The gold Cadillac? You're shitting me.
你扯蛋吧，那玩意几年没见过了
- Piece of shit hadn't run in years
我讲的是真的
- What'd I tell you?
我的玩意没了，然后就来了一帮家伙说要干掉我
So my blow is gone and now these guys are gonna kill me.
不敢相信是我亲生母亲干的
And my own mother for Christ's sake.
然后。。。
so...?
神马？
- Huh? What?
你会借给我钱的,是吧
- You gonna loan me the money?
没门
- No.
伙计，我够倒霉啦
- Man, I'm fucked.
我这辈子都没有过1000块
I hadn't had $1,000 in my whole life.
怎么会？
How'd you like to?
我怎么听说你有15000？
- How'd you like to have $15,000?
神呐
- Jesus.
别急，听我说
No, just hear me out.
每次都这样，你那农场呢？
Every goddamn time, What about the farm?
别跟我提这茬
Leave the farm out of it.
让我们想点更容易的方法
I'm talking about something way easier than that.
嗯
Ugh!
一定要好一点的
This ought to be good.
你听说过Joe Cooper么？
You ever hear of Joe Cooper?
没有
- No.
他是条子
- He's a cop.
实际上是个警探
A detective, actually.
好吧
Okay.
他也有点自己的小买卖
He's got a little business on the side
他做什么
What's he do?
杀手，杀点人啥滴
He's a killer. He kills people.
好吧，然后？
Yeah. so?
老妈有了一份50000块的人寿保险
Mom's got a $50,000 life insurance policy.
别他妈这样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
好吧，你。。你。。你会怎么想这回事？
Well, who's the...What do you call it?
受益人
Beneficiary.
- Dottie.
- Dottie?
全部的？50000块？
- The whole thing? The whole $50,000?
是啊
- Yup.
她一点都没留给我？
She didn't leave nothing to me?
当然是这样，你个混球，为什么要留给你什么？
Of course not, you dipshit, Why would she do that?
我是她前夫
I'm her ex-husband.
你明白的，老爸，她恨你！
She hates you, Dad. You know that.
那玩意她花了多少钱？
How much something like that cost?
我听说是20
Well, I hear he charges 20.
20000？俄滴神啊
Thousand? Jesus.
听着， 这不是什么我们常说的亲自去分一份的事
Listen, this isn't really something we can cut corners on.
我想说的是，这个不值得亲自动手
I'd say it's worth it not to get caught.
我的意思是，杀手Joe会把它完成的很好的
I mean, Killer Joe's a professional He'll do this right.
你怎么知道的？哪个丫告诉你的？
How do you know? Who told you about this?
这个无关紧要
Never mind that.
我想用保险受益的钱雇用他
I want to hire him on spec Ask him to do it for free
这样实际上它是免费帮我们做的
and then give him a cut of the insurance money.
好吧，我们付清他的钱以后
Well, after we pay this guy
我们净的30000
- and we clear $30,000
- 30 thousand.
我们需要分4份
- We split in four ways
3份
- Three ways.
你怎么算的
- How do you figure?
你，我，我妹
- You, me and Dottie.
Sharla呢？
What about Sharla?
跟她有什么关系？
What about her?
她得分一份
She gets a cut.
她又不是家里的一员
The hell she does, She ain't family.
她比你妈在我身边的时间还常
She's been my wife longer than Adele was.
那是小钱
It's less money.
对你来说是小钱
It's less money for you.
那你就会多拿一份啦
And it's more money for you.
我是家里老大
I'm the father here.
是我找上了她，我是我前妻
I found her, She's my ex-wife.
不是你，也不是你妹
Not you, Not Dottie.
好吧，听你的，分成4份
Okay, fine. We'll just split it four ways.
我也很不爽一无所有，好伐
I ain't agreeing to nothing, okay?
我们谈的是杀人
This is murder we're talking about.
我又不是来听你扯蛋的
I'm not just gonna stand here nodding my head.
让我们换一种看法，她让所有人高兴过么？
Look at it this way. Is she doing anybody any good?
嘛意思？
What do you mean?
有谁关心老妈在不在？
Is anybody gonna care if Mom's not around any more?
是啊，Rex
Yeah. Rex.
那家伙对什么都会吸一鼻子的
Son of a bitch screws anything draws breath.
那也不代表他不关心
- That doesn't mean he doesn't care.
他需要被挑逗一下的
- He'd be tickled pink.
你最好去瞧瞧她怎么对到哪个可怜的家伙
You should see the way she treats that poor bastard.
可能跟当你对付我一样
Probably about the same way she treated me.
怎么才能让我妹过好点
What's better for Dottie?
有10000块，这样她就能进亚马逊中学了
Having $10,000, so she can go to that Amazon school
或者继续跟一个丑陋的，衰老的，酗酒的老妈生活
or having a beat-up, old, ugly, naggy alcoholic mother
继续这样活20年
for another 20 years or so?
我明白了
- I see your point.
太好了
- Exactly.
在我妹不知道我们谈了什么的时候
So long as Dottie never knows what we're talking about.
我们已经开始帮她了
We're really doing her a favour.
是啊
Yeah.
你在做啥
What are you doing here?
跟妈吵了一架
Got in a fight with Mom.
你自己搭建了你的农场？
You build this city all by yourself?
是啊
Yeah.
当然
Sure did.
一块块搭起来的
Brick by brick.
在婚礼的时候我听说了
I heard that at the wedding.
奶奶的，把哥吓尿了
Scared the shit out of me.
梦游真的让人毛骨悚然
Sleep talking gives me the creeps.
是啊，越来越糟了
Yeah. Gotten worse.
每天都会
About every night.
她看不到任何人，是吧
She's not seeing anybody yet?
别害怕
Don't hold your breath.
古人云，那个啥是不会被上身的，那啥？你懂的
Truth be told, I think she's still a... You know.
啥？
What?
处吕？
A virgin?
我会打电话给他
Let me just call him.
至少让我们见面聊聊
And at least just set up a meet and talk to the guy.
我们还没最终决定。
We don't got to decide anything right now.
- ANSEL Okay.
- Okay. good.
我听到你们讨论杀老妈的事
I heard y'all talking about killing Momma.
我想这是个好主意
I think it's a good idea.
好吧，我看行
Well, there you go.
我们谈的是谋杀
This is murder we're talking about.
那会很困难
That looks hard.
你是谁
Who are you?
Joe Cooper. Joe Cooper.
你把姐吓尿了
You scared me to death.
对不起
Excuse me.
我道歉
And I apologise.
我敲了门，你电视太大声了
I knocked on the door, but you had the TV on too loud
我就决定自己进来了
to hear me, so I decided to let myself in.
好吧
It's okay.
从电视上学那会很困难
That looks hard. From a TV like that.
你应该找个老师
You should have a teacher.
我是Joe Copper
I'm Joe Cooper.
我是来见Chris的，我们约的10点半
I'm supposed to meet Chris here at 10:30.
他不在
He's not here.
我是来得早了点
Well, I'm a little early.
他通常都会迟到的
He's usually late.
我能麻烦你倒杯咔灰么？
Could I trouble you for a cup of coffee?
当然
Sure.
请坐，让我帮你把外套挂起来
Why don't you sit down and I'll take your jacket.
嗯，谢谢
Mmm-hmm. Thank you.
你叫啥？
Can I ask your name?
我是Dottie
I'm Dottie.
你好，Dottie
Hello, Dottie.
你好
Hi.
啥？
What?
你是啥来着？
What are you?
我是问，你干啥来着？
I mean, what do you do?
我是警探
I'm a detective.
真的？
- Really?
嗯
- Mmm-hmm.
像侦探玛格农（1980米国电视剧）
Like Magnum P.I?
不
No.
他是私家侦探
He's a private detective.
我是达拉斯警探
I'm in the Dallas Police Department.
他是虚构的
- He ain't real, either...
是啊
- No.
我是真的
I'm real.
书里的汽车追逐都很刺激
I read it's nothing like them shows with car chases and all.
看的很仔细啊
A lot of paperwork.
书里的很多警探
I read some policemen go their whole lives
一辈子都没开过枪
without shooting their guns.
那可能是真的
Probably true.
你从来没有丢掉过你的枪？
- You ever drawn your gun?
当然
- Oh, sure.
你有射过谁么？
You ever shot anybody?
。。。有
- Yes.
谁？
- Who?
你不认识
Nobody you'd know.
射死了么？
Did they die?
。。。是啊，死了
Well, they have. Yes.
Wow.
这辈子最刺激的事是神马？
What's the most exciting thing that's ever happened?
唔。。。。
Hmm.
我走进了一所房子。。。
I went into this house.
听到可怕的惊叫声
I heard an awful screaming coming from
从后面传出
inside in the back.
那里一片黑暗
And it was pitch dark.
于是我好奇的跟着惊叫声来到了后面的卧室
So I followed the sound of the scream back to a bedroom.
但是我不知道会有什么在那里等待着我
And I didn't kno what the hell to expect.
Yeah.
当我打开门，突然。。。哇！
When I opened the door suddenly just... Whap!
有个胖子
There's this huge, fat man
在我头顶
was on top of me.
尖叫着，挣扎着
- Screaming and kicking and clawing
俄滴神啊！
- Oh, my God.
我看到的是
And the thing was,
这里空空荡荡没有其他人
there was nobody else even there.
他没有恶意，只是想我帮帮他
And he wasn't trying to hurt me, He wanted me to help him.
为啥？
Why?
你看， 他只是跟她铝盆友吵了一架
See, he got into a fight with his girlfriend, right?
因为她被发现劈了腿
She'd been having an affair, so...
为了教训一下她
In order to teach her a lesson.
他说的
That's what he said.
为了教训一下她
"Teach her a lesson."
他把鸡鸡插入了某种溶液
He doused his genitals with lighter fluid
并点上了火
and he set them on fire.
你相信么？
You believe that?
那是真的
It's true.
那个脑残的家伙点着了自己的鸡鸡
That poor miserable bastard set his own genitals on fire
只是想教训一下他的铝盆友
just to teach his girlfriend a lesson.
我想他铝盆友看过了
I guess he showed her.
我只是想知道那个铝的能否接受眼前的一切
I wonder if she ever got over it.
他还好么？
- Was he all right?
不
- No.
不，他一点一不all right
No, he was not all right.
你的鸡鸡烧了
He set his genitals on fire.
我有个阿姨有次也把自己烧着了
I had an aunt who set herself on fire once.
是吗？
Yeah?
不是故意的，当时她穿着长蕾丝裙子
Not on purpose, though. She was wearing this long lace dress
被火炉给勾住了
and she got it caught in the furnace.
在他们铺面火焰之前，她就屎了
She died before they could put the fire out.
是吗？
Really?
他们说，他是这个家族中我长得最像的人
They say she's the one in the family I look the most like.
他叫Vivah，一个很好听的名字。
Her name was Vivah. Isn't that a pretty name?
唔
Mmm-hmm.
我想她还没来得及结婚
I don't think she ever got married, though.
你不接电话么？
You gonna answer that?
那是找你的
It's for you.
我爸正在上班
My dad couldn't get away from work.
我想我们是否去Bob Muffler
I was wondering if you could meet us at Bob's Muffler.
那里有什么好地方适合密谈么？
There's some place private where we can talk?
这里有个池塘边的小山坡，下班后
There's a pool hall next door, out of business.
就在哈利 海恩斯旁边
Just off Harry Hines.
带上Dottie，她认得路
Bring Dottie, she'll show you the way.
听着，别再改计划。
Don't change plans on me again.
真的很抱歉
Listen, I'm really sorry.
你再搞大声点吧
Could you try to make a little more noise...
你为什么不来舔舔俺的屁股，杂种！
Why don't you try kissing my ass? Son of a bitch.
你会去杀我妈么？
Are you gonna kill my momma?
不知道
I don't know.
为啥？
- Why?
我得谨慎一点
- I was just curious.
当我很小的时候我妈曾经想杀我
My momma tried to kill me when I was real little.
她放了个枕头在我脸上
She put a pillow over my face,
她关心自己比自己的孩子多
because she cared more about herself than her little baby.
她不象母亲一样爱过我
She didn't love me like a momma should love a little baby.
但是她自己却觉得很满意自己
And she was happy, because she thought she'd done it.
于是我得成长就走向了她自己曾经的那样
And then I couldn't grow into something better than she'd been.
一模一样
Had ever been.
她从来没有，从来不允许我见我得父亲
She hadn't done it. She didn't send me back to Him.
她让我恶心，但是也成功了一小段时间
She just made me sick. Made me not be for a while.
但是我也慢慢明白了
But then I was.
她很失望， 但是也没法改变
She was sad that I was, and I always will be.
你是肿么知道的？
How do you know that?
知道啥？
Know what?
知道你妈想杀你？
That your mother tried to kill you?
我记得啊
Because I remember.
这是我爸， Ansel
This is my father, Ansel.
Ansel.
啤酒？
Like a beer?
不，不了，谢谢
No. No, thank you. Look.
听着，我可没太多时间，所以。。。
I don't have a lot of time, so...
好吧，让我开始吧
Alright Let's get right To it.
假如你们准备好了
If that's all right.
好吧，首先
All right. Well, first Off,
我和我爸从来没做过这个
me and my father never done nothing like this before.
我们也不想做，但是必须发生
We don't want to do it, but it's got to be done.
这跟我没关系
That's got nothing to do with me.
好吧
All right.
好吧，先生
Well, sir
把这段忘掉，也许你能帮我们回答几个疑问
instead of me kicking this off, maybe you could tell us the questions
我们需要提问么？
- we need to ask?
很简单
- It's pretty simple.
你们会负我钱的，是么？
You're gonna pay me for a service that I'm going to perform.
嗯
Uh-huh.
你们会提供她的日程表
You're going to give me the particulars of her schedule.
她日常习惯，我希望有个参照
Her habits. I'll act on them accordingly.
并且，我不会告诉你们我具体行动计划
I won't give you many details on my activities,
因为，你们知道越少
because the less you know,
越不容易被关联进来
the better for everyone involved.
好的
All right.
现在说说我的一些条件
Now I only have a couple of rules that I insist on sticking to.
必须遵守的
- Insist.
好的
- Okay. Yeah.
一旦你们被抓，一旦你们被指认犯了罪
If you're caught, if you're implicated in this crime,
你们要保证不会
you are not under any circumstances to reveal
指认我或者出庭作证
my identity or participation.
哦，当然
Oh, of course.
假如你们违反了
If you break this rule,
总有人会收拾你们
you'll be killed.
你懂的
Do you understand?
- I...
我必须得确认你们明白
- I must be absolutely clear
这些条件
on this point.
我懂了
I understand.
你呢？
Do you understand?
我也懂了
Yeah.
我的报酬是，预付25000，现金
My payment is $25,000 in cash in advance.
必须预付
No exceptions.
- 25?
是的
- Yes, sir.
我听说是20000
- I thought you said 20.
别人告诉我是20000
- I was told 20.
25.
这个，有问题么？
Is that a problem?
没问题，咱不差钱
We don't have a problem with 25 That's not our problem.
那你的问题是神马？
Then what is your problem?
我们有点困难在于，预付
We have a problem with the advance.
不带后付款的
- No exceptions.
听我解释
- Sir, let me explain.
我们决定做这个的一个目的
One of the reasons we're interested in having this done
实际上是我妈有一大笔保险金
is my mother holds a very large insurance policy.
好吧，又一个
They usually do.
我们能保证一定付给你
Now we thought if we can guarantee payment
当我们拿到保险金
after the policy had been covered...
听着，这个没得谈
Look, this really isn't open for discussion.
谈话结束
- The conversation is finished.
蛋定，蛋定
- Please. this isn't...
你以为你们在干嘛？
What did you think this was huh?
你能接受麽？
Let's Make A Deal?
这是严肃的事情，别tm在这里扯蛋了
This is serious business you're fucking with here, boy.
我真的明白
- I'm aware of that.
不，我不这样认为
- No, I don't think you are.
你并没有认真听我说
I don't take you seriously.
总会有各种方法去完成的
This is gonna get done one way or another.
我们的谈话到此结束
Our conversation is finished. I never met you.
你们从没见过我
You never met me.
当然，我们也没机会讨论什么预付“好处费”
Of course, we never discussed the possibility of a retainer.
你这啥意思？
What do you mean?
你知道肿么找到我
You know how to reach me.
给我电话，假如她真感兴趣
Call me if she's interested.
嘿，你说的是我妹？
Hey, man, you talking about my sister?
当然是你妹啊
Is that who she is?
俄滴神啊
Jesus.
他神马意思 “retainer”
What's he mean, "retainer"?
你以为，他说的是我妹啊
What do you think he means? He means Dottie.
我是问神马是Retainer
But retain what exactly?
你脑残么？你真的不知道？
Just how stupid are you? Are you really that stupid?
注意你的语气
- Watch your fucking mouth!
这下我们肿么办，老爹？
- What are we gonna do, Dad? Huh?
让我们再想想
We gotta think of something.
我们自己也能干掉她
- We could kill her ourselves!
你真的准备去杀人？
- Are you gonna kill somebody?
你连手表都不会看
You can't even tell time!
那好，你倒是告诉我要肿么办，小屁孩儿
Well, what do you suggest, smart-ass?
好吧，事情总会过去的
Well, we can forget about the whole thing.
或许。。。
Or we can
我们可以给他 Dottie
give him Dottie.
是啊，也许对她也是好事
Yeah, it might just do her some good.
别傻了，没人会再见到他们了
Don't be silly. Nobody's ever gonna see them.
你担心个毛线
What are you so worried about anyway?
你又不会见到他们
It's not like you can see your face in any of them.
你在唠嗑？
- Personal call?
- Uh-uh
两个大号意大利腊肠披萨
Two large pepperoni pizzas, please.
冲印店就在商场后面
That photo shop behind the mall.
你担心太多了
You worry too much.
只是些满脸疙瘩的青涩小铝孩
Just some pimply-faced lime girl
谁没见过一两回
who never seen one before in her life.
没啥大不了的事
Nothing that big anyway.
你多久来接我
What time you gonna pick me up?
8点半？那你还指望我能做什么？
8:30? What do you expect me to do until then?
等等，Jenny
Hold on, Jenny.
能给点钱给我吃晚饭么？
Can I have some money so I can fix supper?
Jenny，下班后我给你电话
Jenny, I gotta call you after my shift.
现在不行。。。
I can't' I have to... Yeah.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
你准备吃什么？
What are you fixing for supper tonight?
一些烩面吧
- Just some casserole.
你会做点色拉么？
- You gonna make a salad?
嗯
Mmm-mmm.
我会给你点钱
Why don't I give you a few extra dollars?
去打扮一下你自己
Get yourself a new dress.
我们会有位客人
- We're having a guest for supper.
那我们需要打扮一下么？
- Do we have to dress up?
你打扮起来一定很漂亮
I'm just saying you'd look real pretty in a dress.
那是你男盆友么？
Was it your boyfriend on the phone?
啥意思？
What do you mean?
那是你男盆友么？
That wasn't your boyfriend?
傻瓜，我结婚啦
- I'm married, silly.
我不会告诉老爸的
- I won't tell Daddy.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
那是Jenny，我高中的朋友
That was Jenny, an old friend from high school.
拿着
Here you go.
我说过了，不要黑橄榄
I said no black Olives.
再做一个超霸，不要黑橄榄，我得休息一下
Fire up another supreme. No black olives. I'm taking my break.
吃吧
- Eat.
他帅么
- Is he cute?
别再谈这个了
Stop talking like that.
又应该找个帅锅
You should have a cute boyfriend.
三年级的时候有一个
I had a boyfriend in the third grade.
我从没告诉任何人
I never told nobody.
他叫马歇尔，很胖
His name was Marshall. He was fat.
他爱我
He loved me.
你需要经常出来走走
You need to go out more often.
没人知道我们在一起了
Nobody ever knew we were going together.
在休息区我们也分开走，吃午饭也不坐在一起
We didn't see each other at recess, we didn't sit together at lunch.
我们也不传纸条，他也从不送我回家
We never wrote notes and he didn't walk me home from school.
那你们在哪里见面啊
When would you see him?
学校上课的时候
In class, at school.
我是说，私下里见面
I mean, alone.
我们没私下见面过
We didn't see each other alone.
从来都没有？
- Ever?
那会暴露的
- That would have spoiled the secret.
那你怎么确定你们在一起了？
How'd you know you were going together,
假如你们从来不私下做点什么？
if you never spent any time alone?
我们很明白
We just knew. If we talked about it,
一旦我们谈起那回事，最纯真的东西就会变味道
it wouldn't have been what it was, which was true
神马纯真的东东？
What was true?
爱 我们之间的爱
Love. We loved each other.
你怎么能知道他爱你呢？如果互相都不交谈
How do you know he loved you, if y'all never talked about it?
因为那是最纯洁的爱
Because he loved me with pure love.
好吧
Well,
我猜，不会再有了
not many like that around, I guess.
是Joe？Joe来过了
It's Joe, isn't it? Joe's coming over.
Joe 谁
Joe who?
不记得了
I don't remember.
他眼神很毒
His eyes hurt.
唔？
Huh?
啥？
What?
见过他？
- Met him?
唔。。。
- Mmm-hmm.
他长啥样？
What's he like?
他告诉我，我应该找个功夫老师
He told me I should get a teacher for my kung fu.
是吗？
Yeah?
而且他还喝了我做的咔灰
And he had me make him some coffee.
他人怎么样
- What's he like?
我不清楚
- I don't know.
Hey, Ansel.
记得忘掉Jenny，她只是高中的一个老朋友
Now you just forget about Jenny She's an old friend
我可不想你爸知道
and I don't need any trouble from your daddy
只是老朋友，记得了吧
over an old friend, you hear?
你应该找个帅哥
- You should have a cute boyfriend.
- Shh!
嘿，你们在谈我么？
Hey, y'all talking about me?
你个耳背的老家伙
- Your ears must've been burning.
真没有
- No, sir.
我只是告诉Dottie她打扮起来一定很好看
I was just telling Dottie here how pretty she'd look in a new dress.
是啊，待会我可以带你去Thrifty
Yeah, I'll ride you over to the Thrifty
然后漂漂亮亮的把你接回来。
and maybe we'll pick you out something pretty, all right?
所有事的办妥了么？
Is everyone getting dressed up?
是啊，都搞定了
Yeah, we're all getting dressed up.
嘿，能给点钱我么？啤酒喝光了
Hey, can I get some money? We're out of beer.
我钱包在楼下
My purse is downstairs.
你什么时候告诉这倒霉孩子，这事就Joe和她？
When are you gonna tell that girl it's just gonna be her and Joe?
她自己会明白的
- She'll figure it out
你要去告诉她
- You gotta tell her.
这倒霉孩子与众不同
That girl's not like other people.
俄滴神，这孩子少根筋
God damn it, she don't put two and two together
她不明白会发生什么
like you, me and Chris.
你担心个毛线
What are you so worried about?
他甚至都没约会过
She never been on a date before.
那不是约会
- It ain't a date.
是啊，龌龊的私密
- It's the closest thing
这辈子也不会再有了
she'll ever come to one.
除了单恋一个永远不知情的胖子
Except for some fat kid that didn't even know it.
虾米胖子？
What fat kid?
你要告诉她
You talk to that girl
你有责任安排好所有事
else you're liable to blow this whole thing real good.
我该说点啥？
- What am I supposed to say?
告诉她整个故事
- Tell her the story, for God's sake.
为神马你要把整件事搞得更加复杂呢？
Why do you have to make everything so difficult?
神马故事
- What story?
当前的状况
- The situation.
告诉她为神马Joe今晚会来
Tell her why Joe is coming over tonight.
为什么我要那样做
- How am I supposed to get to that?
假如她不知道
- If she don't know
她会把事情搞砸的
what's expected of her, she might disappoint him.
把她送到Thrifty，是吧
I'm riding her over to the Thrifty, ain't I?
Ugh!
那我的酒钱呢？ Sharla
What about my beer money? ...Sharla.
胖子？
What fat kid?
希望你带上你的长矛了
Hope you have a spare.
老爸
Daddy?
Daddy.
嘿，嘿，看呐
Hey, hey, look at you.
你看起来像个电影明星
You look like a goddamn movie star.
转个身
Turn around.
看起来真的像电影明星
Yeah, just like a goddamn movie star.
我觉得很可笑
I feel funny.
哦，别介，你看起来很漂亮
Oh, don't say that, You look beautiful.
我的屁股太肥了
My butt's too big.
让我告诉你些大屁股铝淫的小秘密
Well, let me let you in on a little secret.
那些大屁股
- Guys like big butts
哪有
- They do not.
都是真的
I'm speaking from experience.
Sharla没有大屁股
Sharla doesn't have a big butt.
是啊，她会有的
Yeah, well, give her some time.
你肿么还不换衣服
Why aren't you dressed yet?
我不会假如你们的晚餐的
'Cause I'm not gonna stay for supper.
啥意思？
What do you mean?
你哥和我有些事要做
Chris and I got some business to attend to
我哥在哪？
Where's Chris?
所以，就你和Joe留下来吃晚饭
So it's just gonna be you and Joe for supper.
那我要换回来
- I should change.
不，不
- No. No.
不用，亲爱的
- No. honey.
不，我要换掉
- Yeah, I should.
Dottie，Joe假如看到你这么漂亮，会比较好
Dottie, I think it'd be nice for Joe, if he saw you looking pretty.
不，我要去换。。。
- Yeah, I'm going to...
听着，亲爱的
- Listen, honey. Dottie!
蛋定，Dottie
- Just settle down. Dottie!
让我换掉吧
- Let go of me, I have to change!
等等
- Dottie, wait a second!
换掉！我一定要换掉！
- Change! I have to change!
我一定得换掉
I have to change!
Dottie 别关门
Dottie' don't close that fucking door on me.
我一定得换掉
I have to change!
该死的
God damn it!
等等，你个倒霉的孩子
Hold still, you little bitch.
发生了什么
- What the hell's going on in here?
咋咧
- What the fuck!
发生了神马事？
What the hell's going on?
她一定要换掉她身上的裙子
- She wants to take off her dress.
然后？
- So?
你不觉得她穿裙子会更漂亮一点么？
Well, don't you think she looks nice?
让她换呗，你随便穿上点什么
Let her change, if she wants. You put on whatever you like.
你不觉得她很漂亮么？
- Don't you think she looks nice?
嘿，别管他了，老爸
- Hey, let her change, Dad!
让她换
Let her change!
等等
- Hang on a goddamn second.
- Hey
让她换
Let her change....Change.
你们为什么还在这？
What are you doing here?
我们正要出去
We're on our way out.
我们已经谈过了
- We discussed this.
别猴急，我们在走
- Well, don't push it. We're leaving.
是的，别性急
That's right, junior. Don't push it.
现在，我们可以开始后面的事了
Now, we make arrangements,
我希望看到你们认真的去找到一些有用信息
I expect the details to have some attention paid to them.
我们走，老爸
Let's go, Dad.
明白了吗？
You understand?
Yeah.
好孩子
Good boy.
她在哪？
Where is she?
换衣服
She's changing.
他要是遇上Sharla就好了
Too bad he didn't meet Sharla first.
他要看不上，我也不会很在意
He could've dated her, I wouldn't have minded so much.
那是我老婆，你个倒霉孩子
That's my wife you're talking about, fuck head.
你对
Yeah. Right.
Dottie?
是我
It's me, Joe Cooper.
你哥他们走了
We're alone now.
你不出来也行
You don't wanna come out, it's okay.
你可以呆在里面
You stay in there as long as you like.
烩面闻起来不错
Casserole smells nice.
我希望能找到一个你感兴趣的约会故事
I wish I had a funny story about first dates
但我没有
or casseroles, but I don't.
或许我会有一个
Maybe one will come to me.
或许没有
Maybe not.
Lee Hazlewood. Okie from Muskogee.
我也不认识什么Lee Hazlewood
I don't have a funny story about Lee Hazlewood, either.
或者什么奥克拉河马的故事
Or Oklahoma.
倒是有些奥克拉河马的趣事
I guess Oklahoma's kind of funny anyway though.
哥是从遥望着奥克拉河马的
I grew up, looking at Oklahoma.
红河南岸长大的
From the south bank of the Red River.
小的时候记得
When I was a boy, the border between Texas
德克萨斯和奥克拉河马的分界实际就是河的中间
and Oklahoma was actually the middle of the river.
在北岸钓鱼，鱼就是奥克拉河马的
You fish the north bank, you caught Okie fish.
我是在德州钓鱼的
I caught Texas fish.
在某一个时候，德州放弃了这边的半个河岸
Sometime since then, we gave our half of the river away.
现在，整条河都属于奥克拉河马了
Now the whole damn thing belongs to Oklahoma.
南岸
South bank.
现在成为边界了
That's the border now.
哥不明白为什么这样做
I'm not sure why we did that.
那些事让我很郁闷
But it makes me mad.
听起来很像放弃了
Ifs kind of like giving away
你家门前的走廊
your front porch.
你还好吗？
- How are you?
很好
- Fine.
你不想知道我怎么样了？
You wanna know how I am?
你好妈？
How are you?
我很好
I'm fine. Thank you.
你看起来真漂亮
You look nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
我换过衣服了
I changed.
我不知道只有你和我一起吃晚饭
I didn't know it was just gonna be you and me for dinner
他们应该告诉你的
Someone should have told you.
他们刚告诉我
They did Just now.
你刚才换了什么？
What did you change from?
一条裙子
A dress.
那应该很漂亮
I'd love to see it.
你眼神很毒
Your eyes hurt.
请你原谅
I beg your pardon?
Dottie，你相信我吗？
Dottie, do you trust me?
不
Not quite.
好的
Good.
很可爱
Lovely.
我还是处铝
I'm a virgin.
哥知道
I know.
Ay!
三文鱼烩面
- Tuna casserole.
是啊
- Yes.
能开动了吗
- May I serve?
- Please.
谢谢
Thank you.
Mmm.
哥还是想看看那套裙子
I'd really like to see that dress.
那个不好看
It wasn't right.
能看看么
May I see it anyway?
你准备怎么干掉我妈？
How you gonna kill my momma?
这个不适合晚餐的时候谈，是吧
That's not appropriate dinner conversation, Dottie.
至少你可以下药
Unless you poison her.
你会被委任去调查这案件么?
Will you be the detective who investigates?
不会
Probably not.
也可能是
Sometimes.
那是个问题么
Is that a problem?
那会是个机会（一语双关-很舒适）
That's convenience.
就当是你家吧
So are homes.
Yes.
我喜欢我哥
I love my brother.
记得老爸老妈离婚的时候
I remember when Momma and Daddy were getting a divorce.
她仅仅告诉我们，她当时喝醉了
She just told us. She was drunk.
她说 我不再爱你们的父亲了
She said, "I don't love your daddy no more".
我也从未爱过他
"I never loved him."
我尖叫这也起不了任何作用
And I screamed something that didn't make any sense.
于是我跑到前面的院子里
Ran out of the house to the front yard.
我哥也出来了，没说话
Chris came out. He hadn't said anything.
他只是面对面的把我压在下面，像这样
He just laid on top of me. He stretched his body out like this.
把我压住知道我停止哭泣
Laid on top of me till I stopped crying.
- Dottie...
我们从未提起过
We never talked about it ever.
穿上那裙子
Bring the dress.
现在？
- Now?
是啊
- Yes.
为什你不能为我穿上它呢？
Why wouldn't you wear that for me?
那不是我
'Cause it's not me.
这个没半毛钱关系
Not when you're not in it.
我曾有个男盆友
- I once had a boyfriend.
穿上它
- Put it on.
好吧
Alright.
你去哪？
Where are you going?
我去换裙子
- I was going to put on the dress.
我说穿上它
- I said put it on.
我是要去啊
I was.
在这
Here.
我想看看
I wanna see you put it on.
停
Stop.
把袜子脱了
Take off your socks.
脱掉你的胸罩
Take off your brassiere.
脱掉你的内裤
Take off your underwear.
造小孩？
Babies?
穿上裙子
Put on the dress.
过来
Come here.
到我后面来
Right behind me.
把手放进我的裤裆里
Put your hand inside my pants.
你摸到了吗
Do you feel that?
是啊
Yes.
神马感脚？
What's that feel like?
不记得
I don't remember.
你多大了？
How old are you now?
12.
我也是
So am I.
换我来
Switch places with me.
你的男盆友？
Your boyfriend?
马歇尔
- Marshall.
他很胖
He was fat.
Uh-huh.
他在精神上爱我
He loved me with pure love.
这是我们的秘密
It was our secret.
没人知道
Nobody.
Oh.
快啊！
Come on!
1000下5号Nose，和8号 Lone star
1,000 on On the Nose, on 5 on the eighth at Lone Star.
广播 前六是
ANNOUNCER On My Mind there in sixth.
And it's Mango, Cliff, Rick's Café
很远之外是Bella Luna
and way, way back there, Bella Luna.
不到半英里了，他们进入大弯道
Less than half a mile to go as they move into the far turn.
Betty Boo在外侧领先于Nose，
Betty Boo leads a nose on the outside. Yes I Can...
现在看来也仅仅是小小的领先
It's still Tilt a Whirl with a tenuous lead.
Legal Tender and Endearing Manners
继续超前，在外道的是8号
strikes the front just outside the eighth pole.
快啊，5号
Come on, 5.
Cavalier 在弯道中间处于落后
Cavalier coming down hard the centre of the track
麦克老爹也在那里
and Daddy Mike is right there.
快啊5号，快！
- Come on, 5. Come on, 5, come on 5!
进入直道
- Towards the inside,
快啊，超过他们
- coming on through
该死的
- Piece of shit.
Endearing Manner上来了
...but it's Endearing Manner that's come on now
领先啦
- to take the lead as they come...
它被挡在了身后
- He held back!
进入冲刺了
- And in a spectacular finish...
它被挡在身后
- He held back!
一次完美的加速，Endering Mannaer 赢得了胜利
A spectacular upset, Endearing Manner has won the impossible!
孤星17比1的冷门得到了证实
17 to 1, resolved at Lone Star here today.
去屎！
God damn, motherfuck!
- Hey.
时间到了，兄弟
- Time's up brother.
三周前你就要求一周的延长了
You asked for an extra week three weeks ago brother.
你曾说过你有个计划
- You told me you had a plan
不，听着，我打过你电话
- No, listen, I called you.
11点我打过你电话
- I called you at 11:00
这是你所谓的计划么？
- This the plan?
别这样，G 哥
Come on, G-Man.
是啊，钱会在。。。
Yeah, the money is coming to you by about, Motherfucking...
杂种
Son of a bitch!
倒霉孩子
You little motherfucker!
你去哪里
Where you going?
该死
Piece of shit!
瞧瞧这个！
Here you go, here you go!
Chris.
Hi Digger.
最近如何，孩子
How you been, boy?
还好，你呢？
Pretty good. How about yourself?
挺好
Oh, fair to middling.
血压很高
Blood pressure.
看过医生？
You taking medicine?
是啊，不能吃咸的，别有压力
Yeah, alt that. No salt, low stress.
当然，Amy还是在做炸鸡，你知道我没法抗拒的
Course, Amy keeps making that fried chicken. You know I can't resist it.
Amy还好么？
How is Amy?
她破产啦
Well, she's all busted up right at the moment.
你还记得Dumpling，那个老家伙
You remember Dumpling, that old bluetick we had?
是啊，记得
Yeah, sure, Dumpling.
好吧，听着我们昨个早上让他下课了
Yeah, well, we had to put him to sleep yesterday morning
- Oh, no.
- Yup.
真遗憾你错过了一个Party
Well, you missed yourself a hell of a party
几周前
a couple of weeks ago.
对不起，我错过了你的生日
Sorry I missed your birthday.
实话，我很高兴你没来
Well, I'm glad you missed my birthday.
我只是希望你来参加我们的Party
I just wish you hadn't missed the party.
G哥，我们当时有多少人？
How many people we have out there at the place, G-Man?
百十来好
A couple hundred.
没多少啊
Oh, hell, it wasn't that many.
150总是有的
- 150 anyway.
- No shit.
很遗憾我错过了
Sorry l missed it.
是啊，很不错的聚会，很多烧烤
Yeah, good old party. Lots of barbeque.
嘿，G哥当时还表演了手风琴
Hey, G-Man here, he played the accordion.
那就对了
That's right.
嘿，那个铝的当时在场么？
- Hey, wasn't that gal out there?
哪一个？
- What gal?
那个总围着Chris转的铝孩
Well, the one that's always sniffing around Chris's shit here.
叫啥？
What the hell's her name?
有个很大厨房的那个铝的。。。
The one with the great big caboose on her...
- Arlene?
- Arlene.
是啊，Arlene
Yeah, Arlene.
你最好找找她，她很适合你
You'd better look out for her, boy. She may be too much woman for you.
她最好离烧烤远点
Well, she'd better stay away from the barbeque
要不然她会太女人了以致出不了那扇门（暗指很肥）
or she'd be too much woman to fit through the door.
嘿，太逗了
Damn, you make me laugh.
听着，我是来说服这个倒霉孩子别找你麻烦
Hey, listen, I'm just gonna have the boys here kick the shit out of you.
你最好这几天就把钱还给我
You'd better pay me my money in a couple of days
要不我会把你用胶布缠起来
or I'm gonna wrap you up in electrician tape
然后把你活埋了，你的明白？
and bury you in a coffin about 10 feet deep. Huh?
我会转告Amy你的问候
I'll tell Amy you asked about her.
那至少会让她开心
That'll make her smile.
他真心喜欢你
He really likes you.
趴着别动
- Stay the hell down!
对不起
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
慢点慢点
- Easy, Easy.
俄滴神啊，发生了什么
- Oh, my God, what happened?
该死的
- Fuck!
Chris，你看起来很差劲
- Chris! Shit. You look rough, boy.
老家伙抓到你了
Them old boys caught up to you huh.
爸！我想他们打断了我的手
Dad! I think they broke my hand!
你的脸肿么了
- What did they do to your face?
对不起
- Excuse me.
要送你去医院么？
- You want to go to the hospital?
我想最好送他去
- I think he does.
哥被群殴了
- I got beat up.
你咋滴咧？  - 哥被群殴了
- What happened to you? - I got beat up!
那点湿布来
Can we get a wet rag?
他们怎么你了？
They put the fucking boot to you, or what?
是那个Digger Soames？
That son of a bitch Digger Soames?
他们报了你的菊？
They do all they were going to?
他们要想杀他，他早死了
If they wanted to kill him, he'd be dead.
你鼻子破了
- Your nose is broken.
不止这个
- Is that all?
他们说了什么？
What'd they say to you?
你认为他们会说什么？
What the fuck do you think they said?
我估计他们想要回他们的钱
- I reckon they want their money.
该死
- No shit!
要啤酒么？
Hey, you want a beer?
他们在哪里找到你的？
Where'd they find you?
国王妓院
Fucking Sport of Kings.
你见到Bill了吗？
Did you see Bill there?
我不知道，为啥？
I don't know, why?
他欠我10块
He owes me 10 bucks.
我要睡了，来吧Ansel
I'm going to bed. Come on Ansel.
我们必须去医院
We have to go to the hospital.
不，他没事，仅仅是被揍了一顿
No' he's fine. He just got a whupping.
Ansel！来吧
- Ansel! Come on!
好吧
- All right, then.
我想我要回房了
I guess we're gonna turn in.
Dottie，我们走
Dottie, go on.
晚安Chris
Good night Chris.
我想知道我们现在进展怎样了
I want to know what kind of progress you're making.
正在进行中
It's being taken care of.
好吧
Yeah, right.
你狗日的上了我妹
You've been fucking my sister
我母亲仍然更健康的活着
and my mother's a hell of a lot healthier than me at the moment.
你是想我退出么？讲一声就行
Do you want me off the job? Say the word.
你计划多久行动？
When are you planning on doing it?
今晚
Tonight.
真的？
Really?
然后你明天就离开了？
So you'd be leaving tomorrow then?
不不不，好处费仅仅是抵消后付款的
No, no, no, the retainer's for the money.
我要等到拿到钱再走
I'm not leaving until I get my money.
我可不喜欢这个
I don't like that.
我可不在乎
Well, I don't care.
我不想你接近我妹
I don't want you near my sister.
我不在乎
I don't care.
加入我告诉你交易取消？
And if I tell you the deal's off?
我会立刻离开，你也永远看不到我
Then I'll leave right now and you'll never see me again.
你的决定
Your call.
你欠谁的钱？
Who you into for this money?
我不会说
I won't tell you.
Digger Soames?
你怎么知道？
How'd you know that?
加入你不还给他，他会怎么对付你来着？
What did he say he'd do to you, if you don't pay him?
你也知道的
You know that too?
他会动手的
He'll do it.
你会拘捕承诺杀人的人么？
Aren't you supposed to arrest people who commit murder?
我喜欢Digger
I like Digger.
去抓他
Do it.
- Mr Tim.
- Hey Joe.
Joe, Joe. Thank God.
我还担心我不能到达这里，我来的太晚了
I was afraid I wouldn't get here. I'd be too late, Thank God.
听着，我们得停止这一切。
Listen, we got to stop this. Alright?
我已经有很多麻烦了
I've been in a lot of trouble all my life,
但是我从没放弃过
but I never did nothing like this before.
对不起了，我可不想浪费你的时间
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to waste your time.
我是说，我恨她，我一直都恨她
I mean, I hate that bitch. I always hated her.
我可不能上我妹，你明白的
I just can't be the one, you know?
但是真正的问题还是Dottie
But the main thing really is Dottie.
我妹可从来没做过白给的事，你也明白的
You know, my sister never did nothing to nobody.
- (CAR LOCK BEEPS}
你要说服她放弃
- You got to give her up,
我可不想再见到她了
'cause I can't look her in the eyes otherwise.
我是说你可不能拥有她，不能
I mean, you can't have her. I can't let you have her.
你要做什么？去哪里？
What are you doing? Where are you going?
上车
Hop in.
该死
Shit. OW!
Fuck!
我曾有个农场，那也是我梦想生活的样子
I started a farm once. It seemed like the life I wanted.
为我自己忙碌着，吸吸大麻悠闲地在农村生活。
Work for myself outside a lot. Live in the country, smoke dope.
看看电视，这一切都是我的梦想，所以我开了个养兔的农场
Watch TV. That's all I really want. So I started a rabbit farm.
我靠自己的双手搭建了农场
I built it with my own two hands.
装卸站，围栏，水塔，排管，以及兔子
Lumber, chicken wire, water bottles, pellets, rabbits.
我喜欢那些可爱的小家伙
I loved those little bastards.
他们总是微笑着嘿休嘿休一整天
They smell like shit and they fuck all the time,
但是太容易招引野兽了
but they're awful easy going animals.
老鼠，臭鼬或者其他的都很容易进来
A rat, a skunk or something got into the pen
那是些鲜活的兔子
and it was rabid and awful hot out too.
于是他们撕开了每一只兔子
And they just tore each other up.
眼球满地乱滚，口中一面尖叫着一面吐着血泡
Their eyes rolling and foaming at the mouth and screaming.
你听过兔子的尖叫么？像极了小铝孩
You know rabbits scream? They sound just like little girls.
那完全被打乱了
I mean, it was disturbing.
我开始贩卖毒品，我很了解这个。。。
I started selling dope for a living. I knew more about it, so...
我没钱还给他们，也不想还给他们
So I can't pay this guy and I don't even really want to.
你必须离开， Joe
You gotta get out Joe.
你必须永远的离开我妹
You gotta leave my sister alone forever.
这都肿么了
What's going on?
Jesus.
慢点
Easy.
把她的脚放在地板上
- Put her feet on the floorboard.
- Alright.
好了吗？
- Alright?
好了
- Yeah.
把这个放回行李箱去
Put that in the trunk and shut it.
来点光
Give me some light.
我正在看电视，Chris
- I was watching that, Chris.
听着
- Listen.
我正在看电视
- I was watching a show.
我知道
- I know.
我想看看结局
- I wanted to see how it turned out!
他没完成那任务，明白吗？
- He don't catch the bird, okay?
他会没完没了的继续
- It just goes on and on and on.
那又尊样？
- Yeah?
听着，亲爱的
Listen, honey.
我知道，你清楚下面要发生什么
I know, you know what's going on, okay?
我没有机会亲自解释你听
I don't got to explain it to you.
唔
Mmm-hmm.
假如我能明白爱因斯坦的相对论
If I'd known how this would all fall out
我一定会选择另一条路
I might have done things different.
不
No.
出什么问题了
What's wrong?
俄滴神啊
For God's sake.
该死
Shit.
各位早安
- Good Morning y'all.
早安
- Good morning.
Morning.
她的中间姓氏， Ansel？
What was her maiden name, Ansel?
我需要填进表格里
I need it for the file.
好的，Rogers
Yes, sir. Rogers.
Adele Carolyn Rogers.
这个需要预审么？
- Is there gonna be a trial?
不
- No. No.
Joe知道他应该做什么
- Joe knows what he's doing.
我可总来没被审讯过
- I ain't never been to a trial.
你在报纸上见过枪击案么？或亲眼看到在她车里发生
Did you see the shot in the paper? Her car?
Joe知道要做什么，他们不会进行尸检的
Joe knows what he's doing' all right? They couldn't do no autopsy,
因为并没有什么值得特别调查的
'cause there wasn't much left to speak of.
进展怎么样了？
- How'd it go?
让我们先离开这里
- Let's just get out of here.
小杂种
- Little son of a bitch.
嘛事？
- What's the matter?
我不想当着Dottie说
I am not talking in front of Dottie.
她早就知道了
She knows what's going on.
我不想当着Dottie说
- I'm not talking in front of her.
刚才发生了什么？
- What happened with Filpatrick?
我TM不想当着Dottie说
I ain't talking in front of Dottie!
他们不会给你那笔钱的，是吗？
They're not gonna pay you the money, are they?
老爸？
- Dad?
Ansel，蛋定
- Ansel, calm down.
老爸
- Dad?
Ansel！别说话！
- Ansel! Don't make a scene!
谁告诉你，你妈有什么保险？
Who told you about Adele's policy?
Rex！Rex说的
Rex! Rex told me.
他在有次谈话的时候提起来的，你能不能。。。。
He just mentioned it in conversation. Will you, for the love of God...
多久？
When?
一次谈话
- In conversation.
多久？
- Not how, when?
几个星期前，我和老妈刚吵了架
A few weeks ago. Me and Mom just had a big fight...
哦，天呐
- Oh, Christ.
我说过，Ansel
- I told you, Ansel.
咋咧？
- What happened?
我就知道
- I told you from the start.
闭嘴！  -  别叫我闭嘴！
- Shut up! - Don't tell me to shut up!
又不是我挑起整件事情的
- I'm not the one who blew this thing.
出了啥事了啊？
- What happened, Dad?
你到我家来，告诉每个人该干什么
You show up at our place, tell everyone what to do.
我们如何去挣那几千块！
How we're all gonna see a hundred grand!
该死的，快告诉我发生了什么
God damn it, you tell me right now.
Dottie不是最终受益人
Dottie is not the beneficiary!
Rex是最终受益人  - 我不明白
- Rex is the beneficiary!  - I don't understand.
那还不算什么  --给我再解释解释
- It's not real tough. - Explain it to me.
Dottie得不到那笔钱
Dottie does not get the money.
Rex会得到那笔钱。  - 蛋定，蛋定
- Rex gets the money. - Wait.
Dottie得不到那50000，倒霉的孩子！
Dottie does not get $50,000 boy!
Rex! Rex!
Rex会得到那50000块
Rex gets the $50,000.
- That's not right.
- That's the way it is! That can't be.
你自己去问Filpatrick！ - 我被告知！
- Go talk to Filpatrick yourself! - I was told!
他告诉我的！
Because he told me!
Rex告诉我的，他说的！
Rex told me, he told me!
Rex是老妈的男盆友
Rex was Momma's boyfriend.
闭嘴Dottie，他明明是这样说的！
Just shut up Dottie, He told me!
他说慌了！ - 为什么要这样做？ - 那还用想么？
- He was lying. - Why would he do that? - Why do you think?
不会的！他根本不知道我会这样做。
No. No, he couldn't have known I'd do this.
谁告诉你的杀手Joe
Who told you about Killer Joe?
哦
Oh.
哦，天呐
Oh, God.
我告诉你的。 - 是啊， 是我告诉你的么？
I told you. - Yeah. Did I tell you?
俄滴神啊，我被玩弄了
Oh my God, I'm fucked.
MD！MD！MD！
Piece of fucking fuck-suck-cake!
我不相信你
I don't believe you God.
你最好相信
You'd better believe it!
因为你会的，你一会儿就能明白
'Cause the sooner you believe it, the sooner you figure out a way
还要付杀手Joe的钱！
to pay Killer Joe his money!
我们走吧
- We gotta get going.
还别提有个Digger Soames
- Not to mention Digger Soames.
我们不走吗 - 为虾米？
- Gotta get going y'all. - For what?
葬礼在半小时后开始
Funeral's in a half hour.
你们去吧，我得好好想想
Y'all get going. I gotta think of something.
希望你能想明白
I wish you would.
你要想通了，我们也好过点
We're all so much better off whenever you do.
Joe在哪？他会回来的，是吧
Where's Joe? He's coming back, isn't he?
是的
Yeah.
他会回来的
- He's coming back all right.
他一定会回来的
- Yeah, he's coming back all right.
我们马上就要跟你妈在地下会合了
Let's hit it. We gotta get your mother in the ground
我带Dottie走。 - Dottie！
- I'll take Dottie. - Dottie!
是啊，我们自己去
Yeah, we'll be along.
Smith小姐，你见过香薰过的地狱之门么？
Ms Smith, when you're done fumigating the gates of hell.
嘿，Chris
Hey, Chris.
帮我们一个忙！
Why don't you do us all a big favour?
去屎！
Just go kill yourself.
你不舒服么？
Do you feel bad?
是啊
Yeah.
我感觉，仿佛是时候回火星去了
I feel like maybe I'm not supposed to be on Earth or something.
你还记得他们教你肿么方你的膝盖么？
Do you remember them shows you used to put on with your knees?
唔？
Huh?
我们得躺在床上，拿着手电筒，把膝盖弯曲朝上
We'd be laying in bed and you'd get a flashlight and put your knees up
在一边放上一副墨镜
and put a pair of sunglasses on one knee
另一边放上帽子
and some kind of hat on the other?
是啊
Yeah.
再接着是一段表演
Put on a little show.
最伟大的表演，我记得你是这样叫的
"Greatest Show on Earth“ is what you called it.
是么？
Yeah?
进入时间的永恒，从现在起，再没有颠沛流离
Into time and forever, from now on, no more adventures,
- 没有时间的终结或者国王的谢幕
time outs or king's exes.
在最后你会重复的念道
Everlasting one more time than you can say,
进入无尽的虚空，阿门
into infinity and outer space, Amen.
后悔是最可怕的
Nothing's worse than regret.
癌症，被鲨鱼吃掉都不可怕
Not cancer, not being eaten by a shark, nothing.
Joe 会回来的，是吧？ 因为。。。
Joe's coming back isn't he? 'Cause I...
我想离开
I'm leaving.
我在想也许 - 我想你能跟我一起走
- I think maybe... - I want you to come with me.
去哪？
Where?
墨西哥
Mexico.
不，更远，秘鲁
No, further. Peru.
在南美
In South America.
我们怎么去？  -  开车去
- How we gonna get there? - We'll drive.
我们能开车去
We can drive it.
Chris 。。。- 你不喜欢德州么？
- Chris... - Do you like Texas?
很多人都说那里很不错
These people talk about it like it's such a great place and all,
实际上就是一帮土炮，和红番
but it's really just a bunch of goddamn hicks and rednecks,
有一大片开阔地
with too much space to walk around in!
而且很温暖 - 我们走吧
- It's warm. - Let's go.
我们走吧
Let's just go.
现在 - 去葬礼
- Now. - To the funeral?
嘿，假如我们去了就回不来了
Hey, if we're gonna pull this off we gotta gas up.
我必须见Joe - 不，Dottie
- I have to see Joe. - No, Dottie.
我必须见他
I have to see him.
我们必须去秘鲁，现在！
We have to go to Peru now!
那你自己上路吧 我必须见Joe
Well, then you go by yourself. 'Cause I have to see Joe!
我们来做个约定
I'll make you a deal.
我们去葬礼，然后你再见Joe
We'll go to the funeral and you can see Joe after.
不开玩笑，我保证
No funny stuff, Promise.
你发誓
You swear?
我发誓
I swear.
你不能告诉Joe，我们会去秘鲁。
You can't tell Joe we're going to Peru, okay?
你不能跟他说再见，至少别直说！
You can't tell him goodbye, not outright.
好吧
- Okie-dokie.
你也不能告诉老爸和Sharla
And you can't tell Dad or Sharla, either,
因为他们正在气头上，一定会破坏我的计划的
'cause they're mad at me right now and might try to spoil our trip.
明白了
- I understand.
你高兴么？ 跟我走？
You excited? You wanna go?
我一直都很兴奋
I'm always excited.
我们能成功的，我们能甩开这一切
We can do this. We can pull this off.
有人让我郁闷，我也会不高兴的
Not if somebody makes me mad.
Rex甚至都没来，这个狗杂种
Rex didn't even bother to show up. Son of a bitch.
请您俯身近来，凝听我们的声音
Bow down thy ear to me. Deliver me speedily.
请赐予我坚固的石墙，保护我
Be thou my strong rock for a house of defence to save me.
我将再次关荣的笼罩于您的慈悲之下
I would be glad to rejoice in thy mercy.
您将免去我一切的烦恼
For thou has considered my trouble.
拯救我的灵魂与逆境之中
Thou has known my soul in adversities.
您将从敌人的千军万马中拯救我
And thou has not shut me up into the hand of the enemy.
并与许我踏入主，光荣的殿堂
Thou has set my feet in the Lord's room.
请宽容我，主啊！
Have mercy on me, oh, Lord.
我将被世人所遗忘
I am forgotten as a dead man out of mind.
我们聚集于此，乞求永恒的长眠
We are gathered here to put to eternal rest
Adele Carolyn Rogers-Smith.
两个孩子深爱的母亲（讽刺啊），克里斯托夫 和 桃乐兮
Beloved mother of two children, Christopher and Dorothy.
以及家族所有成员和朋友们
Devoted to her family and community.
嘿，Rex
Hey Rex.
手放车上
Hands on the car.
去你的，屁眼 - 随你便
- Fucking asshole. - Whatever.
Dottie!
是我们
It's us!
我们在KFC吃了饭，你饿了吗？
We stopped by the K-Fry-C. You hungry?
Dottie!
Chris!
嘿，递我一瓶啤酒  -  他不在家里
- Hey. Fetch me a beer, would you? - He's not here.
嘿，Joe  - Dottie在么？
- Hey Joe. - Dottie here?
她睡了
She's asleep.
Chris在哪？  -  我不知道
- Where's Chris? - I don't know.
你来点炸鸡？我们吃的KFC
Do you want some chicken? We stopped by the K-Fry-C.
当然，谢谢
Yes, please.
自己动手，在炉子上
Sure, help yourself. It's right here on the stove.
递给他一下好吗 ？
Fetch it for him, would you, hon?
当然，嫩的还是老点的？
Sure, white or dark?
腿
Leg.
啤酒？
You want a beer?
好的
Yes, please.
把那架在桌上
Set that on the table, please?
谢啦  - 唔
- Thank you. - Mmm-hmm.
葬礼总是让人觉得饿
Funerals make people hungry for some reason.
唔
Huh.
我快饿死了
I'm starving.
嗯
Mmm.
你听说过保险？  -  Sharla
- You hear about the insurance? - Sharla.
是啊，听过  - 我不知道怎么说
- Yes, I did. - I don't know what to say.
你不需要说什么，我知道那不是你的错
You don't have to say anything. It's not your fault.
是啊，但是。。。 - Chris
- Yeah, but - Chris.
Chris是个脑残，我必须告诉你，这家伙把事情搞砸了
That Chris is so stupid, I could have told you he'd fuck this up.
你难道没有么？  - 我什么？
- Why didn't you? - Why didn't I?
那只是发泄，真的
It's just an expression, really.
神马？
What is?
她想说， Chris是个脑残，这家伙把事情搞砸了
What she said. That she could have told you Chris would fuck it up.
我可从没听过这种抱怨
I've never heard of that expression.
一种很礼貌的说法
- A manner of speaking, really.
我可从没喜欢过那倒霉的孩子
- I never liked that little bastard.
你从来没有？  - 嗯
- You haven't? - Mmm-mmm.
他确实不怎么好，你没法相信他
He's just no good. You can't trust him.
你从没说出来过
- You never really hit it off.
他只关心他自己
- All he cares about is himself.
这不公平
- That's not fair.
去TM的公平，那是事实
- Bullshit fair, it's true.
人们总是关心心里想的事情，这是事实
It's really all anybody cares about if you think about it.
不感兴趣。  - 不感兴趣什么？
- No wonder. - No wonder what?
不感兴趣Chris是否喜欢他自己
No wonder Chris wound up the way he did.
那我做了什么？  -  闭嘴吧！
- What the fuck did I do? - Just shut up.
我是说你当初有多傻
I mean, how stupid do you have to be
被Rex这白痴给耍了
to let an idiot like Rex take advantage?
Rex？ - 是啊 Rex
- Rex? - Yeah, Rex.
Rex怎么了？  - 我是说。。。
- What about Rex? - I said...
我是说你当初有多傻，被Rex这白痴给耍了
I said, how stupid do you have to be to let an idiot like Rex
占了便宜 -  我听清楚你说什么了
- take advantage? - Yes, I heard what you said.
告诉我这个Rex - Rex 是Adele的男盆友
- Tell me about Rex. - Rex is Adele's boyfriend.
曾经是
Was.
曾经是Adele 的男盆友
Was Adele's boyfriend.
接着说
Tell me about Rex.
你想知道什么？  - 不是你
- What do you want to know? - Not you.
你  - 神马？
- You. - What?
你，接着说这个Rex
You. Tell me about Rex.
干啥？
What do you mean?
你知道这个人， 我是说你已经见过了
Now, you know the man, don't you? I mean, you have met.
是啊，当然  -  告诉我点其他的
- Yeah, ofcourse. - Tell me about him.
我不明白你啥意思
I don't know what you mean.
高矮胖瘦？或者是个中国人？
Is he tall? is he fat? is he Chinese?
在哪工作？多大年纪？他穿耳洞么？
Where does he work, how old is he, do his ears hang low?
他有什么特征？说说这个Rex
Is he unlike other men? Tell me about Rex.
Rex是
Rex is..
我还是不明白
I don't get this, really.
谁告诉你了这些安排？
Who told you about our arrangement?
什么安排？
What arrangement?
这家里，谁告诉你这些事情？
The contract between myself and this family?
Ansel - 肿么了？
- Ansel. - Why?
她是我堂客 Joe
Well, she is my wife. Joe.
我没问你，先生  - 好吧
- I wasn't addressing you, sir. - Okay.
他为啥要告诉你？
- Why did he tell you?
就像他说的，我是他喔理想（扬州话）
- I'm his wife, like he said.
你也想分一份么？
Were you gonna get a cut of this money?
当然  - 啥不对么？
- Sure. - Why?
我必尽是他老婆
'Cause I'm his wife, like he said.
你当初有反对Ansel做这个么？
Did you advise Ansel against the idea?
木有
No.
为虾米？
Why?
你有说过Chris会把整件事搞砸么？
You could have told him Chris would fuck it up.
跟我半毛钱关系都没有
It's none of my business.
但是却是跟你有关系，不是么？
But it is, isn't it?
我是说，那是你的问题
I mean, it is your business.
那你又会做什么？
What are you getting at?
既然你也想分一份
If you were going to share in the money,
这就跟你有关了，不是么？
then it is your business, isn't it?
是啊，我不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
所以你没有反对这计划，对吧
Yet you did not advise Ansel, your husband, against it?
是啊，我却是想得到一份
Look, I wanted some of that money alright.
假如，只是假如，Chris真的能成，我可以。。。
If... If, Chris could pull this off, then I...
可以分得你老公的一份？
Were you gonna split Ansel's share?
或者你们可以平分4份
or were the four of you gonna split it evenly?
我们没讨论过。  -  我肯定你们讨论过
- We didn't discuss that. - I'm sure you did.
你是很实际的女人
You're a practical woman.
好吧，假设我能分到4分之1
Well, I assumed that I would take a fourth.
不是一半或者3分之1？
Not one-half of one-third?
不是，是4分之1
- No, a fourth, four ways.
不是6分之1
- Instead of one-sixth.
6分之1
One-sixth.
不，4分之1
No. Four ways.
所以剩下的钱会被分开
So the remainder of the money
当你们付给我的我要的费用以后
would be split evenly after I'd been paid my fee.
- $25,000.
是的，是的
- Right, right. Right.
是啊，得在你的费用付清之后
- Yeah, right after you were covered.
平分
- Which means equal shares.
那这平分的4分从哪里来呢？
What would those four equal shares come out to?
我可没算过
- I haven't done the math.
现在马上给我算算
- Well then do it with me. Right now.
我们拿到了那笔保险金
The insurance policy gets covered.
Filpatrick给了Ansel一张支票
The agent Filpatrick cuts Ansel a cheque.
Dottie，那是属于Dottie的
Dottie, That would be Dottie.
好吧，好听一点，Dottie
Right, best of all possible worlds, Dottie.
看吧，我不知道为什么我们做了这些个烂事
Look, I don't know why we're doing all this.
我们一毛也拿不到
We're not gonna see any of that money.
看着我的脚
Just watch my feet here, alright?
好吧
Alright. Mhmm.
Ansel确实拿到了支票
- So Ansel gets the cheque.
- Dottie.
看吧，假设这支票是100000
- Look, if the cheque is for 100,
我们付你25000
We Pay you 25.
多少？
- How much?
- 25.
这保险金总共有多少？
How much, though, the policy is for?
多少？说啊多少？
However much. How much?
- 50 thousand.
就这么多？
- That much.
50000减去25000
- 50 minus your 25.
对，减去我的25000
- Right, minus my 25,
但是你说有100000，是么？
but you said 100, didn't you?
是，无论多少，先减去你的
Yeah, however much, minus your money.
不，你说有100000
No, but you said 100.
是的，无论多少
- Yeah, however much.
支票上是100000
- The cheque is for 100.
不管多少  -  但你说有100000
- However much. - But you said 100.
无论多少，减去你的25000
However much, minus your 25.
Joe她算错了，只有50000
She was mistaken, Joe. It's 50.
对吗？
Alright?
是吗？
Is it?
是的
Yeah.
像Dracula里面的女巫一样围着棍子转圈
Stick around for witches as Christopher Lee
以揭露恐怖旅馆里的女巫大会？
unearths a whole coven at the Horror Hotel.
还是继续加入我们从小镇出发的马拉松？ -狗日的编剧为了前面一段脑残般的胡搅
蛮缠开始洋洋得意的引用起电影场景了
Join us for more of our George Raft marathon. Starting with Whistle Stop.
去屎！快点！
Fuck! Come on!
是不是？
Isn't it?
不
No.
等等
Wait a minute!
假如是事故死亡，赔偿是双倍的
In case of accidental death, the figures double.
是啊， Filpatrick早上告诉我们的，不是吗？Ansel
Right, Filpatrick told us that this morning, didn't he Ansel?
啊！ - 是啊，他说过
- Nah ah. - Yeah, I think he did.
Ansel?
他说过么？
Did he?
不  -  我记得他说过
- No. - I think he did.
然后。。。
So...
那就不是5W？  - 不
- It's not 50? - No.
那是10W
It's 100.
我说过，不管多少  - 无论多少
- Like I say, however much. - However much.
看吧，你都做了什么？
- Look, what are you getting at?
神马意思？
- What do you mean?
我犯了个错误
- I made a mistake alright?
是啊
- Yes, you did.
我说是5W 或者 10W，无论多少 - 嗯
- I said 50 or 100. However much. - Mmm-hmm.
你们继续算
Y'all gonna do this now?
你说过，你不关心Chris
You said that you never cared for Chris.
是的，一点也不
I haven't, I don't.
你也说过Rex是个白痴
And you also said that Rex is an idiot.
是的
Yeah, right.
你还说过，支票上写着10W
And you also said that the cheque was for 100.
无论多少！
Or however much!
我只是好奇
- I was just wondering.
你做了什么？
- What are you getting at?
该死！
Oh fuck.
这是谁的鸡鸡？
Whose dick is that?
你从哪里弄来的？
Where did you get those?
这不是Ansel的
That's not Ansel's dick.
是你的么？Ansel
Is that your dick, Ansel?
不是
No.
是我的，亲爱的，你喝多了！
Yes, it is, darling. You were drunk.
那一个呢？
How about that one?
也不是
Nope.
这一个？
That one?
你要确定哦，你可能喝多了
Make sure now, you might have been drunk.
绝对不可能  - 唔
- No. - Hmm.
这是谁的鸡鸡？
Whose dick is it?
住手！
You just stop that.
这绝对是你男盆友的
- That must be your boyfriend.
哦，别介
- Oh, please.
你男盆友Rex
- Your boyfriend Rex.
哦，别介
- Oh, please now.
那个白痴，那个拿走所有钱的白痴
That idiot. The one who's getting all that money.
我不知道  -  所有的10W
- I didn't know! - All 100 grand.
住手，我发誓，我什么都不知道
Just stop it! I didn't know anything about this, I swear.
你知道这些么？ Ansel
Were you aware of this, Ansel?
我一点也不知道
- I'm never aware.
当然
- Of course not.
这是谁的？
Whose is it?
你个狗日的日本人！
You son of a bitch!
别直呼姓名好伐，我都没叫你的名字
There's no need for name calling. I haven't called you any names.
我是客人，你要有点礼貌
I am a guest here, You be polite.
现在
Now.
告诉我们，这鸡鸡是谁的，别想骗我
Whose little dick is that, and do not lie to me.
你要是想骗我，这将是你最后一个谎言
You lie to me, and it will be the last lie you ever tell.
Rex的  -  Rex的？
- Rex. - Rex?
那是Rex的  - 你确定？
- It's Rex - Who?
Rex！ - 回答正确
- Rex! - Correct.
Ansel，救救我！
Ansel, please!
Ansel不会帮你的在这一点上
Ansel is not too inclined to assist you at this point in time.
是吧，Ansel
Are you Ansel?
是的，我不会
No, I'm not.
实际上，Ansel做得很好，只是安静的站在那里
In fact, Ansel's doing just fine standing over there.
是的，先生
Yes sir.
那也是我所想的
That's what I thought.
放开我，你个日本人！
- Let me go, you motherfucker!
我刚说了什么，你要再侮辱我的话？
- What did I say about insulting me?
我们会给你钱的，我发誓
We'll give you the money, I swear it.
我们会给你，你想要多少都行
We'll give you as much money as you want!
我恐怕那不可能
I'm afraid that's impossible.
不，不会的
No. ifs not.
Rex 下午就走了
Rex picked up the settlement this afternoon.
神马？
What?
他走之前把支票留给我了
He gave it to me before he left.
10W
100 grand.
全能的主啊
God Almighty.
他去哪里了？
Where did he go?
当然，对Rex来说，这些都没用了
Worthless, of course. It's made out to Rex.
他说他要去哪里？
Where did he say he was going?
他已经不能说什么了
- He was unavailable for comment.
我不明白
- I don't understand.
你为什么不把他带到。。。
Why didn't you get him to...
是的，我能找到他
I can...
我能找到他
I can get him.
看来你需要一个新男盆友
Looks like you need a new boyfriend.
我会成为你的新男友，不过就那么一会
I'll be your boyfriend, just for a little while.
躺着别动
Just stay down.
躺下
Stay down.
看着我
Look at me.
吸这个
Suck this.
自己打手枪去！
Go fuck yourself!
假如你再侮辱我！
If you insult me again,
我会把你脸撕下来，戴在我的脸上
I will cut your face off and wear it over my own.
明白了？
Do you understand?
Ansel!
你自找的
You made your bed.
对啊
That's right.
躺下吧
Now lie in it.
吸这个！
Now suck it!
求求你！
Please.
你想我切下你的脸？
Do you want me to wear your face?
吸这个
Now suck it.
慢点
Easy.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, Here we go.
Alright.
Hey.
Hey!
你在想什么？
What do you think?
我木有啊！
I don't!
听着，你们俩！
Now listen carefully, both of you.
我完成了你们给的任务
I performed a service for this family.
我应该得到全额报酬
And I deserve my payment in full.
因为一些小误会
Because of a misunderstanding with the insurance,
我并没有得到我的报酬
I won't receive any cash for my services.
这不公平
That is unfair.
我可不在乎你们对于这次过失的借口
I don't care to hear excuses or placement of the blame.
我对你们一视同仁
I hold you all equally responsible.
抱住我的屁屁
Reach around and grab my ass.
在这里，抓住屁屁，就这样！
There you go. Grab it, That's it.
我是幸运的，不过换一种思维
I was fortunate, however, in thinking ahead.
我救回了我应得的报酬
I secured a retainer for my services.
我已经尽到了我的责任
Since I fulfilled my obligation,
我也无法得到我的现金
and since my cash is not forthcoming,
这些“报酬”应该是我的了
that retainer is now mine.
都是我的
It belongs to me.
我会把它都带走
and I'm taking it with me when I leave.
你很在行啊，继续
You're very good at this. Please moan.
Chris并没同意给你这些奖励啊
Chris doesn't agree with the concept of the retainer.
他晚上会来的，并且会带走她
He's coming here tonight to attempt to take it with him.
我不会允许的
I can't,
不允许他那样做
allow him to do that.
你们不能
This family can't allow him
允许他那样做
to do that!
我们必须走了
We have to go.
那让我窒息
It's suffocating me.
我永远也见不到他们了
I can't be around them any more.
你明白么？
Do you understand me?
我要把你们都杀掉！
I'll slaughter all of you!
假如你们让Chris离开这个拖车的话
If this family allows Chris to leave this trailer,
我会把你们都杀掉
I'll slaughter all of you like pigs!
你们相信我吗？
Do you believe I'd do that?
我在请求你们的帮助
I am asking for your help.
你们会把她给我的
Will you give it to me?
Ansel?
是，先生
Yes, sir.
你现在看起来很漂亮
Now, you're a very beautiful woman.
你不这样看么？Ansel
Don't you think so, Ansel?
我现在什么也没想
I hadn't given it much thought.
错！ - 错误答案！
- No! -
- Wrong answer!
她看起来很漂亮
She's a very beautiful woman.
也很美丽
And that's sweet.
你同意么？
Don't you think so?
慢点
Easy.
现在
Now, hey.
我需要你把厨房打扫一下
- I want you to tidy up the kitchen.
好的
- Okay.
你们会把桌子从新架好的
And you're gonna set the table for a proper meal.
你的明白？
Okay?
搬起那把椅子
Get that chair.
让我们坐下来
And we're all gonna sit down.
吃饭  -  好吧
- for dinner. - Okay.
就我们4个
Just the four of us.
明白了吗？看着我
Understand? Look at me.
就一家人
Just the family.
搬起椅子
Get that chair.
你还好吗？
How you doing, guy?
这照片在哪里拍的？
- Where'd you get them pictures?
那真的很重要
- Oh, that's hardly important.
我猜的话
I guess.
我是说，他只是想含着别人的鸡鸡，从你的口袋里捞钱
I mean, all she did was suck his cock and try and steal your money.
可能会更坏
It could have been worse.
肿么可能？
How?
好吧
Well...
我只是猜想会变得很糟
No, I suppose that's about as bad as it gets.
听着
Listen.
去陪陪你老婆
Go spend some time with your wife.
Sharla.
啥？
Yes?
你还好么？
Are you okay?
是，我还活着，Ansel
Yes, I'm fine, Ansel.
你确定？
Are you sure?
是的，我确定
Yes, I'm sure.
好吧
Okay.
闭嘴，T-Bone
Shut up, T-Bone!
嘿，倒霉孩子
Hey, son.
Dottie在么？  - 在卧室
- Dottie here? - She's in the bedroom.
哦，感谢上帝，我还是到了，Joe来了吗？
Oh thank God, I'm starving. You hear from Joe?
他在他的卧室里
He's in his bedroom.
你吃过了？
You eat already?
Hi Chris.
倒霉孩子
Junior.
你在家
You're home.
Hi, Joe.
我都听说了，关于钱的事
I ehh, heard about the money.
我想告诉你，所有的事都过去了，别妄想把他们从新拼起来
I gotta tell you, I'm all broke up things didn't work out.
我也是
- Yeah me, too.
那是世界的规律，不是么?
- It's the way the world turns, right?
Huh?
就像碎掉的饼干
It's the way the cookie crumbles?
是的
Yeah, okay.
概不退货，你明白的
Caveat emptor, you know what I mean?
我们能吃饭了么？
Shall we dine?
Dear.
笑得灿烂一点，Ansel，Chris，想来点KFC
Smells heavenly. Chris, Ansel, you hungry for some K-Fry-C?
我不是很饿
- I'm not really that hungry.
Ansel你最好来吃点
- Well, you should join us Ansel.
我们全部
All of us.
Chris，坐这边
Chris, have a seat right here.
我们开始吧，
There we go. As it should be.
我们开始吧
There we are.
Sharla，坐下
Sharla, have a seat.
谢谢
Thank you.
这太可爱了
This is lovely.
谁来说祝词
Who would like to say grace?
Dottie， 你愿意来进祝词么？
Dottie. Would you do the honours?
Mmm-hmm.
亲爱的主，感谢您赐予的食物
Dear Jesus, thank you for the food.
感谢您把我们聚集在一起
Thank you that we're all here together and safe.
我们为妈妈的死感到抱歉
We're sorry Momma's dead.
我们希望您能给在天堂里找一个位置
We hope you'll give her a place to stay in heaven.
请宽恕我们一切的
Please forgive us for anything we did wrong.
我们也起到能够在天堂里有个位置--讽刺
We would all like a place to stay in heaven, too.
以全能上帝的名义，阿门
In the Lord's name, which is Jesus Christ, we say, "Amen."
阿门
Amen.
太好了
That was beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
开吃吧，Sharla能给我们拿些喝的么？
Let's eat. Sharla, would you grab us some drinks
再帮Chris那个碟子
and get young Chris a plate please?
白的还是黑的？ - 都行
- White and dark? - Yes please.
Ansel，从那土豆色拉开始好吗？
Ansel, get that potato salad started will you?
土豆色拉
And potato salad.
我喜欢土豆色拉
- I love potato salad.
- And potato salad.
冰红茶，那是你做的么？Sharle？
Iced tea. Is that homemade Sharla?
是的 - 我只要一勺就够了
- Yes, it is. - I only need one scoop of that.
你能帮Dottie盛点土豆色拉么？
Will you get Dottie some potato salad on there, please?
你能先开始吃么？我们会弄多一点的
How about that you start with that and we'll get you some more
好啊  -  太好了，我能开动了么？
if you like. - That's perfect. Can I start now?
请吧，Sharla，白的还是黑的？
- Yes, you may. Sharla, white or dark?
都行
- It doesn't matter.
你想要点土豆色拉？
Do you want some potato salad?
好的
Yes, please.
Sharla，土豆色拉？
- Sharla, potato salad?
够了，谢谢
- No, thanks.
Sharla，你的睫毛膏在融化
- Sharla, your mascara's running.
该死
- Fuck you.
大伙听着
Everybody.
我有件事情想宣布
I have an announcement to make.
你们也许已经注意到了
You've all probably noticed that
我和Dottie在一起共同分享了很多美妙的时光
Dottie and I have been spending an awful lot of time together.
事实上，我们恋爱了
The fact is, we've fallen in love.
所以我有权利告诉大家，我请求她成为我的新娘
So it's my privilege to tell you that I've asked her to be my bride.
她也答应了
And she has accepted.
是吧，亲爱的？
- Haven't you, dear?
是的
- Yes.
这里我想说
- Well i for one would like to say...
闭嘴！
- Shut up.
干杯
A toast.
为我将来的妻子
To my future wife.
这怎么可能发生的？
When's all this supposed to take place?
我们将在这次晚餐后离去
Well, we're leaving right after this delicious meal.
这对么？
Is that right?
是的
Yes.
你不能带走我妹，Joe
You can't have my sister Joe.
Chris，嘛意思？
What do you mean, Chris?
我是说，我不让它发生的
I mean, I can't let it happen.
你不会娶她的
You're not gonna marry my sister.
我想这由不得你
- I don't think ifs up to you.
闭嘴
- Shut up.
别叫我闭嘴
- Don't tell me to shut up.
闭嘴老家伙
- You say another word, old man,
我要把你的头掰下来
and I will rip your head off your shoulders.
现在Chris
Now, Chris,
我能明白你对你妹的爱
I can certainly understand your love for your sister.
但是你需要割断一些陈旧的牵挂
But you got to cut the old apron strings sometimes.
好吧，我不打算讨论这些。她是我妹
Okay, I'm not going to discuss it. She's my sister.
我会带她走的，我们会离开的
I'm taking her with me. We're leaving here.
我们需要Dottie自己决定
We should let Dottie decide.
Dottie没什么要说的
Dottie doesn't have a say tn the matter.
哦，我相信她会有的
- Oh, I believe she does.
你错了
- You believe wrong.
Dottie去收拾你的东西
Dottie' go get your stuff.
Dottie别动
Dottie, stay seated.
Dottie.
别动Dottie
Stay seated. Dottie.
Dottie坐下
Dottie, sit down.
Dottie.
Dottie去收拾你的东西
Dottie. go get your stuff now.
- Dottie.
Dottie.
坚强的铝孩
Ada girl.
Dottie!
她是我的报酬之一
She's my retainer.
交易取消，吃完这口赶快滚
Deal's off. You're gonna have to eat this one.
你明白我可以杀了你
- You know I'll kill you.
打手枪
- Go fuck yourself.
坐下Joe
Take your seat Joe.
Dottie去收拾你的东西
- Dottie, go get your stuff!
Dottie 坐下别动
- Dottie, stay where you are.
这下可好
- This will be just fine.
Dottie去收拾你的东西
- Dottie! Go get your stuff!
住手
Stop it!
Sharla：杀了他Joe！
- SHARLA Kill him Joe!
住手
- Stop it!
JOE!
是
Yes!
住手 Joe
DOTTIE Stop it, Joe!
杀了他！杀了他！
Kill him! Kill him Joe!
我抓住他了，Joe
I got him, Joe!
住手，Joe
- Stop it, Joe!
杀了他！
- Kill him!
- Fucking kill him!
俄滴神啊！
- God! Oh, God!
抓住他！
- Get him!
神啊！
- Oh, God!
我要怒了！
I'm getting angry!
Dottie.
Jesus! Dottie!
Dottie!
慢点
- Easy.
别，Dottie
- Don't, Dottie, Dottie!
放下枪
Put the gun down.
我有孩子啦
I'm going to have a baby.
孩子？
A baby?
一个孩子？
- A baby?
别杀我！
- Please don't kill me!
一个孩子？
A baby?